var questionList = [{
	question: " When did fry get cryogenically frozen?",
	answerList: ["2210", "1999", "2000", "2006"],
	answer: 1
},{
	question: "What Species is Zoidberg?",
	answerList: ["Amazonian", "Nibblonian", "Brain Slug", "Decapodian"],
	answer: 3
},{
	question: "What Food Did Fry Deliver?",
	answerList: ["Italian", "Chinese", "Pizza", "Tacos"],
	answer: 2
},{
	question: "Where is Amy From?",
	answerList: ["Brooklin", "Mars", "China", "Centari B"],
	answer: 1
},{
	question: "Who did Amy marry?",
	answerList: ["Kif Kroker", "Hypno Toad", "Zog", "Morbo"],
	answer: 0
},{
	question: "What is the Ship Zapp Brannigan captains?",
	answerList: ["Planet Express Ship", "Land Titanic", "Kitten Class Attack Ship", "The Nimbus"],
	answer: 3
},{	
	question: "What is Nibler's Poo Made Out of?",
	answerList: ["Gold", "Dark Matter", "Uranium", "Antimatter"],
	answer: 1
},{	
	question: "What century is Futurama set in?",
	answerList: ["21st Century", "24th Century", "31st Century", "40th Century"],
	answer: 2
},{	
	question: "Who Was the creator of Futurama?",
	answerList: ["Chris Sanders", "Matt Groening", "Dan Harmon", "Walt Disney"],
	answer: 1
},{	
	question: "What is the name of the Planet Express's Janitor?",
	answerList: ["Hermes", "Cubert", "Agnew", "Scruffy"],
	answer: 3
}];

//play background song onload
$(document).ready(function() {
	$("#my_audio").get(0).play();
});
//end background song
